influxis.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy - Influxis

Influxis (“Influxis,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the Personal Data it collects. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of how we protect your privacy when accessing or using Influxis’ Services.

This Privacy Policy applies to Influxis’ Services that link to, or reference, this Privacy Policy, and describes the ways Influxis collects and uses your personal information and the choices you have regarding collection, use, maintenance, access and transmission of your personal information. Capitalized terms not expressly defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning found in the Influxis Service Agreement. By utilizing the Influxis Service, including without limitation the website or otherwise providing your Personal Data to Influxis via any other means, you or the entity you represent (“you” or “your”) accept and consent to the rights, obligations and practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Who does the Privacy Policy apply to?**

  * This Privacy Policy applies to all Clients of the Influxis Service, and Visitors to the Influxis website. In the case of Clients, Client shall be responsible for (i) informing their customers (“End Users”), if any, of the existence of this Privacy Policy and (ii) agreeing to this Privacy Policy, as amended, updated or modified from time to time, on behalf of his, her or its End Users.
  * In the case of End Users, (a person who uses a Client’s application or website that incorporates the Influxis Service) Influxis has no direct relationship with such End User and Influxis will not collect their Personal Data directly from them. In the event an End User seeks to access, correct, amend or delete data, the End User should contact Influxis’ Client.
  * If you are a person who has directly signed up with Influxis for the use of Influxis’ Services and you seek to access, correct, amend, or delete data, you should contact Influxis directly. If requested to remove data under either scenario, Influxis will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

**2.** **What Personal Data is Collected by Influxis?**

  * Influxis considers any information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify you to be Personal Data, including without limitation, Personal Data that is accessed, collected, maintained, transmitted and/or used by Influxis in the normal course of our business, and is subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and applicable law.
  * The Personal Data we collect may include, but is not limited to, your full name, email address, phone number, account log-in credentials, billing address, credit card information, IP address and any information you choose to include in your correspondence to Influxis.
  * In the case of an End User, if End User utilizes a Client’s website or application that incorporates Influxis’ Service, depending on how the Client has implemented our Service we may receive End Users’ Personal Data from Client to transmit across our Service and store on behalf of Client. In this case, the End User should direct all requests regarding the Personal Data collected directly to the Client. It is the Client’s responsibility to obtain express consent of End Users to transfer their Personal Data to Influxis. Influxis applies the same security measures as described in Section 7 to End User’s Personal Data received from Client.

**3.** **How is Personal Data Collected by Influxis?**

  * Influxis collects and logs your IP address, the time and duration of your visit, the time and duration of the pages on Influxis’ website that you view (where applicable) and information about your computer system, such as your browser type and operating system, whenever the Influxis Service is accessed or used by you. In the case of Customers, we collect, maintain, transmit and/or use Personal Data provided by you in your Account, including without limitation, your full name, Influxis identification number, billing data and contact information.
  * Influxis utilizes third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our Services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as some personal information like your name and email address) to Zendesk, Inc. (“Zendesk”) and utilize Zendesk as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). For more information on the privacy practices of Zendesk, please visit <https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/>. Zendesk’s services are governed by Zendesk’s terms of use which can be found at <https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/master-subscription-agreement/?cta=msa>. If you would like to opt out of having this information submitted to Zendesk, please email [privacy@influxis.com](mailto:privacy@xirsys.com).
  * Influxis also collects anonymous usage information on Visitors to its website through use of [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/). Google Analytics may employ third party tracking cookies to gather anonymous browser, operating system, geographic, and website navigation information.
  * Use of the Influxis Dashboard interface requires the acceptance of cookies for login session management purposes. Influxis will likely place a cookie on your hard drive during the web visit. A cookie is a unique alphanumeric identifier that Influxis uses to determine the number of unique Visitors that view its website, whether or not those Visitors are repeat Visitors, and the source of the visits. Cookies cannot be executed as code or used to deliver a virus. Other servers cannot read cookies and personal information cannot be gathered from cookies. Cookies are simply an identifier shared between you and Influxis to allow Influxis to improve the services Influxis offers to you through its website. If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your computer, then they can be disabled in your web browser. The option to do so is normally found in your browser’s “security settings” section. However, please note, permanently disabling cookies in your browser may hinder your use of Influxis’ website as well as other website and interactive services.
  * A web beacon, also known as a web bug, is a small graphic (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel), that is embedded in a web advertisement, email, or page on Influxis’ website, which is invisible to you. When you view a page on Influxis’ website, an e-mail or an advertisement, your web browser will request the web beacon from a web server, which in turn will set a cookie in your web browser containing a unique identifier. This unique identifier will be linked to log information that is used to track your usage of Influxis’ website in order to determine the effectiveness of content and advertising campaigns.
  * Influxis does not collect personal information about you as part of a web visit, but web visit information may be tied to other information (including personal information) that Influxis collects from you via chat, web forms, and the other means Influxis describes in this Privacy Policy.

**4\. Why Does Influxis Collect Personal Data?**

  * _For Customers_
  * Influxis may use your Personal Data to handle orders, process your service requests, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, provide access to secure areas of Influxis’ website, and to enable Influxis to review, develop and continually improve the products and services that it provides. Influxis also uses this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of Influxis’ website and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on its behalf.

  * _For Visitors_
  * Influxis uses Personal Data to send information about Influxis to Visitors and to contact them when necessary.  Visitors have discretion as to whether to grant information to Influxis upon Influxis’ request for information.

  * _For Financial Information_
  * Influxis may ask Customers to enter credit card or account information in order to process orders for services placed with Influxis. Financial information provided via its website is transferred over a secure connection via BluePay, Inc., a payment processing company. Influxis does not collect this information and will not authorize the release of the information to anyone not directly involved in processing the transaction. This information may be encrypted and stored for logging purposes by BluePay, Inc.
  * Credit card numbers are used by BluePay, Inc. only for processing payments and are not used for any other purposes. Influxis will ensure that appropriate security and confidentiality measures are in place in safeguarding your personal data.

  * _For Use Information_
  * Influxis uses website use information to measure interest in and develop its web pages and marketing plans, customize the content you view on your web visits based on your activity during past visits, and administer Influxis’ website. In addition:
  * Influxis uses a Visitor’s IP address to help diagnose problems with its servers, and to administer its website.
  * Influxis uses cookies to help it recognize Visitors as unique Visitors when they return to Influxis’ website. Influxis also uses cookies to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interest; avoid showing Visitors the same advertisements repeatedly; compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow Influxis to understand how users use its site and to help it improve the structure of its website (Influxis cannot identify Visitors personally in this way); and count the number of anonymous users of its websites.
  * Influxis uses web beacons to count the number of times that its advertisements and web-based e-mail content are viewed. Influxis combines web beacon information with cookies to track activity on its website originating from advertisements and web-based e-mail content.

  * _For Support Information_
  * Influxis uses information that you provide to it via telephone calls, chat, e-mail, web forms and other communications to correspond with you about services you may be interested in purchasing. If you elect to purchase a service online using a web form, Influxis will use the information to establish your account. Information you submit in writing, such as chat, e-mail, and web form information is archived and may be tied to information that Influxis collects about your web visits.

**5\. Influxis’ Disclosure of Personal Data to Regulatory Agencies**

  * Influxis transfers Personal Data to third parties, including without limitation, law enforcement agencies and consumer reporting agencies, under the following normal business procedures:
  * Influxis uses a Visitor’s IP address to help diagnose problems with its servers, and to administer its website.
  * Influxis uses cookies to help it recognize Visitors as unique Visitors when they return to Influxis’ website. Influxis also uses cookies to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interest; avoid showing Visitors the same advertisements repeatedly; compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow Influxis to understand how users use its site and to help it improve the structure of its website (Influxis cannot identify Visitors personally in this way); and count the number of anonymous users of its websites.
  * Influxis uses web beacons to count the number of times that its advertisements and web-based e-mail content are viewed. Influxis combines web beacon information with cookies to track activity on its website originating from advertisements and web-based e-mail content.
  * If you breach the Service Agreement or other applicable Service Level Agreement, or if Influxis is under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal obligation, Influxis may disclose your information to a relevant authority. Disclosure may include, but is not limited to, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. In particular, Influxis may release the information it collects to third parties when Influxis believes that it is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce its’ legal rights, to protect the rights and safety of others, or to assist with industry efforts to control fraud, spam or other undesirable conduct.
  * Influxis may release the information it collects to third parties, where the information is provided to enable such third party to provide services to Influxis, provided that the third party has agreed to use at least the same level of privacy protections described in this Privacy Policy, and is permitted to use the information only for the purpose of providing services to Influxis.

**6\. User Choice**

  * Subject to applicable law, you have the choice to and right to limit, restrict or deny Influxis’ ability to share your Personal Data with third parties or use of your Personal Data for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose for which it was originally collected or authorized by you. In order to exercise your right to choose, please contact us at privacy@influxis.com, or via postal mail or facsimile using contact information found on Influxis’ [Contact](https://influxis.com/contact/) page. Please note, in the absence of any notice to the contrary, you expressly grant Influxis permission to share your Personal Data at Influxis’ discretion.

**7\. Security, Integrity and Retention of Personal Data**

  * Influxis intends to protect and secure Personal Data, including End User Personal Data that you may transmit through and store on our Service, in accordance to the terms of this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Service, and has implemented physical, administrative and technical measures designed to protect Personal Data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. These industry-standard safeguards include, without limitation, encryption of password and/or cryptographic key-based authentication controls on servers which house personal information, browser-based secure sockets layer encryption, and other storage system access control mechanisms to protect the integrity of internal databases and prevent unauthorized access.
  * It is also your responsibility to ensure authorized access to Personal Data by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your Influxis account.
  * Influxis requires all Influxis business partners and vendors to provide the same or greater protections for any Personal Data that is disclosed by Influxis in furtherance of our provision of the Influxis Service to you. To learn more about Influxis’ contractor requirements, please contact us at [privacy@influxis.com](mailto:privacy@xirsys.com).
  * Influxis retains your Personal Data, including End User Personal Data we may receive, as long as we provide Service to you. We retain Personal Data after we cease providing Service to you, even if you close your Influxis account to the extent necessary to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations. Where we retain data, we do so in accordance with any limitation periods and records retention obligations that are imposed by applicable law.

**8.** **Access to Personal Data**

  * You control access to Personal Data maintained or stored by you via Influxis’ web-based interface for account management. You may update your information at any time. You may cancel your account at any time and may request that your personal information be deleted from Influxis’ databases, with the exception of: (a.) network access logs, which may be stored for any duration of time at Influxis’ discretion, (b.) cases where financially fraudulent or otherwise illegal activity is deemed to have occurred (as determined by Influxis management or law enforcement officials), in which case personal information may be retained indefinitely for purposes of ongoing investigation and prevention of fraud recurrence, or (c.) cases where a violation of the Service Agreement and applicable Service Level Agreement has resulted in cancellation of your account (as defined by revocation of your permission to utilize Influxis’ services), in which case personal information may be retained indefinitely for purposes of prevention of further use of Influxis’ services in the future by the offending individual.
  * Upon request, Influxis will grant you reasonable access to Personal Data maintained by Influxis about you. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to correct, amend or delete information that is demonstrated by you to be inaccurate, incomplete or processed in violation of applicable law. Unless required by law, Influxis will not permit you to access the Personal Data of any data subject other than yourself.
  * If you have any concerns or suspect unauthorized activities associated with your account, please contact us at [privacy@influxis.com](mailto:privacy@xirsys.com). Influxis will respond to all requests regarding Personal Data within a reasonable timeframe.

**9\. International Transfers of Personal Data**

  * Influxis is headquartered in the United States of America (the “US”) and provides its Service internationally. By utilizing the Influxis Service, you expressly consent to Influxis’ access, maintenance, transmission and/or use of your Personal Data outside of your country of residence, regardless of location or jurisdiction.
  * In addition to its obligations under US law, Influxis supplements the protection of the international transfer of your Personal Data by observing numerous industry best practices of data encryption.

**10\. Sensitive Information**

  * Influxis will not intentionally collect or maintain, and requests that you do not provide, any information regarding your medical or health condition, race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or other sensitive information. If you store any data or information that is sensitive and/or violates any other law or regulation, such information and compliance with applicable privacy laws remains solely your responsibility. Influxis is not responsible for any sensitive information stored by you on its system.

**11\. Children’s Online Privacy Protection**

  * Influxis’ services are not designed for or directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age and Influxis will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under thirteen (13) years of age.

**12\. Data Service**

  * You are solely responsible for ensuring compliance with any and all applicable privacy guidelines and regulations for all jurisdictions in which you may operate with respect to appropriate practices for the collection, storage, and dissemination of personal information using the Influxis Service. In no event shall Influxis be held liable for your failure to adopt and/or practice appropriate measures for safeguarding personal information stored within or transmitted through the Influxis Service.

**13\. Dispute Resolution**

  * Please direct any complaints regarding this Privacy Policy to us at privacy@influxis.com, or via postal mail or facsimile using contact information found on Influxis’ Contact page. We will attempt to resolve any such complaints in a reasonably timely manner and in accordance with this policy.

**14\. Enforcement**

  * If you believe your Personal Data has been used in a way that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, or if you have further questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact our Custodian of Records via email or by writing us at the following address:

  * Custodian of Records
  * Influxis
  * 25061 Avenue Stanford, Suite 10
  * Santa Clarita, CA 91355

**15\. Definitions**

  * “Custodian of Records” means the Influxis employee described in Section 14 of this Privacy Policy.
  * “IP” means any internet protocol address, including without limitation, unique and non-unique network addresses.
  * “Personal Data” means any information relating to a data subject that you directly or indirectly provide to us as part of the Influxis Services or any data subject’s use of any Influxis Service.
  * “Privacy Policy” means this policy, as amended at Influxis’ sole and absolute discretion from time to time.
  * “Visitor” or “Visitors” means any individual(s) or entity(ies) that accesses, maintains, transmits, develops, acquires, operates or otherwise uses any Influxis Service but is not a Client.

**16\. Changes**

  * Amendments to this Privacy Policy may be made at any time and you should check back frequently for any changes. Influxis will also provide public notice of amendments to this Privacy Policy on the appropriate Influxis Service. Unless otherwise directed by you in writing to the Custodian of Records, you agree that Influxis shall have the right and ability to amend this Privacy Policy at Influxis’ sole and absolute discretion, and that you waive any requirement for specific or expressed acknowledgement or agreement to any such amendments or modifications. This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.

**17\. Verification**

  * Influxis utilizes the self-assessment approach to assure its compliance with its Privacy Policy. Influxis regularly verifies that the Privacy Policy is accurate and in conformity with applicable local and international law.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.
